In which court is the decision of the court always final?
United States Supreme Court
Virginia Circuit Court
United States Court of Appeals
Virginia General District Court
The Virginia legislature is called the —
General Assembly
State Congress 
State Assembly 
General Congress
In a criminal procedure, which of these is required for an arrest?
Probable cause
Sentencing
Arraignment
Guilty verdict
Issuing search warrants, arrest warrants, and subpoenas is the responsibility of —
magistrates
police chiefs
court attorneys
plaintiffs
Which basic principle of the Constitution of the United States prevents any one branch from gaining too much power?
Checks and balances
Representative government
Popular sovereignty
Rule of law
#


