Which of these is the solution to the equation 5x+7=2(3.5+5x) ?
0
1
-1
All Real Numbers
Which of these number sets is a Pythagorean triple (ie a solution set for the Pythagorean Theorem)?
6,8,10
3,4,6
2,5,7
4,4,5
Which of these transformations could change a nonsquare rectangle into a square?
None of the Above
Translation, then reflection
Reflection, then rotation
Rotation, then reflection
If there are exactly five boys in a 20 person discussion group, what is the ratio of girls to boys?
3:1
5:15
4:1
1:3
Is the number 196 a perfect square? If so, what is the square root? If not, in between what two consective whole numbers does its square root lie?
Yes, 14
Yes, 24
No, 14 and 15
No, 13 and 14
What is the square root of the square root of 81?
3
Not an integer
4
9
What is the solution to the equation 3x+3=4x+4 ?
-1
0
1
No solution
Which set is the same as the set of all whole non-negative rational numbers?
Natural Numbers
Rational Numbers
Integers
Counting Numbers
What is the complementary angle to 33 degrees?
57 degrees
147 degrees
90 degrees
12 degrees
What is the area of the shape formed by the points {(1,1),(4,3),(2,3),(3,1)} ?
4
12
6
9
#