Which of the following is an example of a hypothesis?
If sunlight is increased, then the sunflower's growth will increase.
The sunflower grew 2 centimeters.
Even though sunlight was increased, the sunflower's growth did not increase.
The type of soil was the same for all sunflowers.
Which unit of measurement is for mass?
Grams
Liters
Meters
Pounds
Which of the following is the best example of potential energy?
A book balancing on the edge of a desk
A cow jumping over the moon
A race car speeding around the track
A rock tumbling down a hill
Which of the following is a nonrenewable energy source?
Fossil Fuels
Water
Wind
Sun
Which of the following statements is true?
Warm, moist air rises because it is less dense than cold, dry air
Warm, moist air rises because it is more dense than cold, dry air
Cold, dry air rises because it is less dense than warm, moist air
Cold, dry air and warm, moist air rise at the same time
Which of these is the cause of tides?
Revolution of the Moon around the Earth
Time of Day
Revolution of the Earth around the Sun
Rotation of the Moon
Which space program came first?
Mercury
Gemini
Apollo
The Shuttle Program
Which of these is not a part of atoms?
Positron
Proton
Neutron
Electron
Which of these instruments measures pressure?
Barometer
Thermometer
Anemometer
Hygrometer
Which of these is used to represent an element?
Chemical Symbol
Chemical Formula
Chemical Reaction
Chemical Name
#


